

HaritsSoftware Engineer

+62 821-1288-9474

★ haritsdeveloper@gmail.com

https://linktr.ee/harets

Bogor, Indonesia

SUMMARY

Active youth who has more than one year experience as a Software Developer. Have a digital business team. I am Skilled in Android Application Development and Ui design, experienced on the Web and have knowledge of digital marketing.

EXPERIENCE

11/2021 - Present Head of the Vocational Division

student council of IDN boarding school

05/2022 - 05/2022 Weather Apps

Android Application

Learn to build a weather app using Current Weather Data and 5 Day/3 Hour Forecast from

openweathermap.

IDN Brings Good Impact

Sharing knowledge with other people is something that makes me feel happy, because apart from

being able to help, it can also challenge me to try.

04/2022 - 04/2022 Tech talk about slicing ui with flutter

Weekend Tech Talk Series

In this event I share knowledge about how to create applications with flutter.

01/2022 - 04/2022 We - Muslim 2.0

Kotlin Android Book

Writing a book about an application project that I have made, themed about Islamic activities.

Making the first app with flutter

Build an app using firebase to connect user to another user or real time feature.

EDUCATION

2021 Basic Computer

IDN Bs Junior high school

2nd Place in the Internal Android Application Competition,

Participate in the OTN (National ICT Olympiad) competition

CERTIFICATES

04/2020 - Present Mobile Programming Android & Kotlin

10/2021 - 10/2024 Learn SOLID Programming Principles

09/2019 - 09/2022 Learn to Make Android Apps for Beginners

10/2021 - 11/2021 ITFEST Semifinalist

SKILLS

Kotlin Intermediate Laravel Beginner Firebase NodeJs Intermediate Beginner Android Studio Intermediate Ui/Ux Designer Expert Postman Intermediate Expert Rest API Html Visual Studio Code Advanced Expert Intermediate Java Beginner Git Dart Intermediate Android XML layout Advanced Figma Clean code Intermediate Expert MVVM Intermediate Intermediate **Constraint Layout**

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Indonesia Native